Inventory of the James Robert Huntley papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Atlantic Community: The Democracies, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 142: 2)
- Atlantic Community: Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe (CSCE), 1990-1996 (Box-folder 142: 3)
- International public opinion articles, 1977-1996 (Box-folder 142: 4-5)
- Peace movement, 1981-1999 (Box-folder 142: 6)
- Ploughshares fund, 1984 (Box-folder 142: 7)
- Atlantic Society, 1973-1992 (Box-folder 142: 8)
- Battelle Memorial Institute, Science and human affairs miscellaneous projects, 1973 (Box-folder 142: 9-10)
- NATO press releases, 1985-1996 (Box-folder 143: 1)
- NATO Articles and Papers, 1974-1992 (Box-folder 143: 2-3)
- East-West Relations, 1974-1995 (Box-folder 143: 4-6)
- Atlantic Community, politics and security, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 143: 7-8)
- Atlantic Community, Latin America, 1981 (Box-folder 143: 9)
- NATO defense articles and publications, 1974-2002 (Box-folder 144: 1-6)
- Atlantic Community, Mideast/Arabs, 1975-1995 (Box-folder 145: 1)
- Huntley Congressional Testimony, 1975 (Box-folder 145: 2-3)
- Congressional activity, 1975-1987 (Box-folder 145: 4)
  Includes sound cassette.
- NATO Defense College, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 145: 5)
- NATO Committee on the Challenges of Modern Society (CCMS), 1983-1997 (Box-folder 145: 6)
- Atlantic Community, Atlantic Union, 1947-1996 (Box-folder 145: 7-8)
- NATO: North Atlantic Cooperation Council (NACC), 1996-1998 (Box-folder 146: 1)
- Goodwill Games, 1989 (Box-folder 146: 2)
- East-West relations, 1979-1997 (Box-folder 146: 3-8)
- "Atlantic Commentary: A Prospectus,", 1972 (Box-folder 147: 1)
- "World Politics in the 1980s," (Box-folder 147: 2-3)
- "The European Community in the 1980s," (Box-folder 147: 4-5)
- The Federalist, No. 4 to 8, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 147: 6)
- The Atlantic Council Policy Papers
  - "Alternative Energy Sources for the United States,", undated (Box 148)
  - "What Future for the UN? An Atlantic Dialogue,", undated (Box 148)
  - "Beyond Diplomacy,", undated (Box 148)
  - "Improving NATO Force Capabilities,", undated (Box 148)
  - "What Is the Soviet Navy Up To?,", undated (Box 148)
  - "Détente: The Continuation of Tension by Other Means,", undated (Box 148)
  - "Global Climate Change: U.S.-Japan Cooperative Leadership for Environmental Protection,", 1991 (Box 148)
  - "After the Cold War: U.S. Security for the Future,", 1990 (Box 148)
  - "CSCE: The Diplomacy of Europe Whole and Free,", 1990 (Box 148)
  - "The U.S. Telecommunications Services and Equipment Sector and the European Community Unified Market- 1992,", 1990 (Box 148)
  - "The Common Security Interests of Japan, the United States and NATO,", 1980 (Box 148)
  - "Energy Imperatives for the 1990s," (Box 148)
  - "East-West Relations of the Verge of a New Era: The Revolution of 1989," (Box 148)
  - "Neutralizing the Value of Chemical Weapons,", 1989 (Box 148)
  - "The Downside of the Japanese Economy,", 1989 (Box 148)
  - "Perestroika in the Soviet Union and Western Involvement,", 1989 (Box 148)
  - "The Future of NATO: A European View,", 1989 (Box 148)
  - "Inside the 1988 Federal Budget: Guidelines for American Fiscal Responsibility," (Box 148)
  - "Integrating Economic and Security Factors in East-West Relations,", 1988 (Box 148)
  - "Challenges to Peace and Well-Being: The Problems and Opportunities of the Developed Democracies,", 1988 (Box 148)
  - "The International Monetary System: Progress and Prospectus,", 1977 (Box 148)
  - "Nuclear Fuels Policy,", 1976 (Box 148)
  - "Arms Control and the Gray Area Weapons Systems,", 1978 (Box 148)
  - "Nuclear Power and Nuclear Weapons Proliferation,", undated (Box 148)
  - "The Floating Rate System: The Search for Balance and Stability,", 1978 (Box 148)
  - "Security in the Eastern Mediterranean: Re-thinking American Policy,", 1978 (Box 148)
  - "Securing the Seas: Soviet Naval Challenge and Western Alliance Options,", 1978 (Box 148)
  - "The Growing Dimensions of Security,", 1977 (Box 148)
  - "East-West Trade: Managing Encounter and Accommodation,", 1977 (Box 149)
  - "Nuclear Fuel and American Foreign Policy: Multilateralization for Uranium Enrichment,", 1977 (Box 149)
  - "Recent Works on American Society: An Annotated Bibliography for Educators,", 1984 (Box 149)
  - "Western Interests and the U.S. Policy Options in the Caribbean Basin,", 1983 (Box 149)
  - "The International Monetary System,", 1983 (Box 149)
  - "Arms Control, East-West Relations and the Atlantic Alliance: Closing the Gaps,", 1983 (Box 149)
  - "The Teaching of Values and the Successor Generation,", 1983 (Box 149)
  - "The International Monetary System: Exchange Rates and International Indebtedness,", 1983 (Box 149)
  - "Nuclear Fuels Policy,", 1976 (Box 149)
  - "Towards A Consensus on Military Service,", 1982 (Box 149)
  - "U.S. Energy Policy and U.S. Foreign Policy in the 1980s,", 1981 (Box 149)
  - "Group of Six" Joint Policy Paper: The United States and Japan- Cooperative Leadership for Peace and Global Prosperity, 1989 (Box 149)
  - "Indicators of Change in Soviet Security Policies,", 1989 (Box 149)
  - "Change in Eastern Europe: Soviet Interests and Western Opportunities,", 1989 (Box 149)
  - "Organizing for Change: An Essential Part of Comprehensive Security and Western Prosperity,", 1989 (Box 149)
  - "U.S. International Leadership for the 21st Century,", 1987 (Box 149)
  - "The President, the Congress, and Foreign Policy,", 1985 (Box 149)
  - "National Defense University 1981 Pacific Symposium: Lines of Communication and Security," (Box 149)
  - "Catching the Boat: The 1992 Opportunity,", 1990 (Box 150)
  - "The Role of the Newly Industrializing Economies in the World Economy,", 1989 (Box 150)
  - "European Political Cooperation: Toward a Unified European Foreign Policy,", 1989 (Box 150)
  - "Building an International Investment Accord,", 1989 (Box 150)
  - "Strengthening Interparliamentary Consultation: The Future of the North Atlantic Assembly,", 1983 (Box 150)
  - "GATT Plus: A Proposal for Trade Reform,", 1975 (Box 150)
- "The Annual Meeting of the Trilateral Commission: Copenhagen,", 1995 (Box 150)
- "The Annual Meeting of the Trilateral Commission: Washington,", 1993 (Box 150)
- "The Annual Meeting of the Trilateral Commission: Lisbon,", 1992 (Box 150)
- The Atlantic Council Policy Papers
  - "After Afghanistan: The Long Haul,", 1980 (Box 150)
  - "Summit Meetings and Collective Leadership in the 1980s," (Box 150)
  - "The Soviet Merchant Marine-Economic and Strategic Challenge to the West,", 1979 (Box 150)
  - "Getting the West Out of the Oil Dilemma: An Energy Family Approach,", 1979 (Box 150)
  - "Oil and Turmoil: Western Choices in the Middle East,", 1979 (Box 150)
  - "NATO at 30,", 1979 (Box 150)
  - "The Future of the UN: A Strategy for Like-Minded Nations,", 1977 (Box 150)
  - "China Policy for the Next Decade,", 1983 (Box 150)
  - "The Successor Generation: Its Challenges and Responsibilities,", 1981 (Box 150)
  - "U.S.-Japan Energy Relationships in the 1980s,", 1981 (Box 150)
  - "U.S. Policy Towards Canada: The Neighbor We Cannot Take for Granted,", 1981 (Box 150)
  - "Some Unfinished Business of the Tokyo Round Trade Negotiation: A New Safeguard Code,", 1981 (Box 150)
  - "The International Monetary System in Transition,", 1980 (Box 150)
- "International Education in the Developing State Colleges & Universities,", 1966 (Box 151)
- "The All-in-One Guide to European-Atlantic Organisations,", 1970 (Box 151)
- "Civisme Européen: Documents et Informations Pour L'Enseignement,", 1968-1969 (Box 151)
- The European-Atlantic Movement (T.E.A.M.), library list, 1972 (Box 151)
- "National Stereotypes: An Educational Challenge,", 1968 (Box 151)
- "The USA in the World Economy,", 1966 (Box 151)
- "The USA in the World Economy: Teacher's Manual VI,", 1966 (Box 151)
- "A Teachers' and Students' Guide to Books about European and Atlantic Affairs,", undated (Box 151)
- "Education for Europe: A Handbook for Teachers, No. 4,", 1971 (Box 151)
- "Organising Conferences and Obtaining Speakers,", 1970 (Box 151)
- "The European and Atlantic Communities: A Guide to Source Materials and Teaching Aids,", 1965 (Box 151)
- "The Changing Pattern of the Western World: An Information Handbook,", 1965 (Box 151)
- "The European-Atlantic Movement: Annual Report,", 1964-1965 (Box 151)
- "Education and American History,", 1965 (Box 151)
- "Science and Education: Germany Reports, No. 4,", 1964 (Box 151)
- "The Central Purpose of American Education,", 1961 (Box 151)
- "Education and the Spirit of Science: Educational Policies Commission,", 1966 (Box 151)
- Seminar on the Teaching of Modern Languages, 1966 (Box 151)
- "To Guide Your Rational Planning in Curriculum and Instruction,", undated (Box 151)
- "The European and Atlantic Communities: A Guide to Source Materials and Teaching Aids, 2nd Edition,", 1966 (Box 151)
- "European and Atlantic Academic News,", 1967 (Box 151)
- "The Professional School and World Affairs: Report of the Task Force on Education,", 1967 (Box 151)
- "Citizens of Europe: A Bulletin of Contemporary European Studies for Teachers,", 1966-1971 (Box 151)
- "The Code of Ethics of the Education Profession,", 1963 (Box 151)
- "21st Century Strategies of the Trilateral Countries: In Concert or Conflict? A Report to the Trilateral Commission,", 1999 (Box 152)
- "International Economic Policy: Europe, North America, Latin America," papers from the 1972 Atlantic Conference (Box 152)
- "L'Impédieratif Industriel,", 1970 (Box 152)
- "The President, the Congress, and Foreign Policy,", 1986 (Box 152)
- "Educational Technology: The Design and Implementation of Learning Systems,", 1971 (Box 152)
- "Centre for Educational Research and Innovation: Purpose, Programmes, Progress,", 1970 (Box 152)
- "University of London: General Information for External Students,", 1969 (Box 152)
- "Technische Hogeschool Twente,", undated (Box 152)
- "Delta: A Review of Arts Life and Thought in the Netherlands,", 1965 (Box 152)
- "Twente Technological University: A Campus University, 1963 (Box 152)
- "Five Years Technische Hogeschool Twente,", 1966 (Box 152)
- "Kwartaalbericht N.O.I.B.,", 1968 (Box 152)
- "The University of Sussex: Guide for Applicants, BA and B Sc Degrees,", 1968 (Box 152)
- "The Graduate School: The London School of Economics and Political Science,", 1969 (Box 152)
- "The London School of Economics and Political Science: Handbook of Undergraduate Courses,", 1970 (Box 152)
- Aiglon Association News, 1968 (Box 152)
- Aiglon College, undated (Box 152)
- "The Educational Interchange Council: Annual Report and Accounts,", 1968 (Box 152)
- "U.S. College-Sponsored Programs Abroad,", 1974 (Box 152)
- The Triangle Papers
  - "No. 15: An Overview of East-West Relations,", 1978 (Box 153)
  - "No. 13: Collaboration With Communist Countries in Managing Global Problems: An Examination of the Options,", 1977 (Box 153)
  - "No. 12: The Problem of International Consultations,", 1976 (Box 153)
  - "No. 9: A New Regime for the Oceans,", 1976 (Box 153)
  - "No. 7: OPEC, The Trilateral World, and the Developing Countries: New Arrangements for Cooperation, 1976-1980,", 1975 (Box 153)
  - "No. 6: Energy: A Strategy for International Action,", 1974 (Box 153)
  - "No. 5: Energy: The Imperative for a Trilateral Approach,", 1974 (Box 153)
  - "No. 4: Directions for World Trade in the Nineteen-Seventies,", 1974 (Box 153)
  - "No. 3: A Turning Point in North-South Economic Relations,", 1974 (Box 153)
  - "No. 2: The Crisis of International Cooperation,", 1973 (Box 153)
  - "No. 50: Managing the International System Over the Next Ten Years: Three Essays; A Report to the Trilateral Commission,", 1997 (Box 153)
  - "No. 37: International Financial Integration: The Policy Challenges; A Report to the Trilateral Commission,", 1989 (Box 153)
  - "No. 36: East-West Relations; A Report to the Trilateral Commission,", 1989 (Box 153)
  - "No. 25: Sharing International Responsibilities; A Report to the Trilateral Commission", 1983 (Box 153)
  - "No. 22: The Middle East and The Trilateral Countries,", 1981 (Box 153)
  - "No. 21: Trade in Manufactured Products with Developing Countries: Reinforcing North-South Partnership,", 1981 (Box 153)
  - "No. 19: Industrial Policy and the International Economy,", 1979 (Box 153)
  - "No. 18: Collective Bargaining and Employee Participation in Western Europe, North America and Japan,", 1979 (Box 153)
  - "No. 17: Energy: Managing the Transition,", 1978 (Box 153)
  - "No. 16: Reducing Malnutrition in Developing Countries: Increasing Rice Production in South and Southeast Asia,", 1978 (Box 153)
- Atlantic Community, general security, 1980-2003 (Box-folder 154: 1-4)
- Atlantic Community, general NATO, 1978-2002 (Box-folder 154: 5-7)
- International Joint Commission, 1965 (Box-folder 155: 1)
- Atlantic Community, space, 1980-1989 (Box-folder 155: 2)
- The Marshall Plan, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 155: 3)
- NATO, General, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 155: 4-6)
- Europe bibliographies, 1974-2002 (Box-folder 155: 7)
- Security, 1990-2003 (Box-folder 155: 8-10)
- Western Europe Union, 1954-1992 (Box-folder 156: 1-2)
- Strasbourg Conference on Parliamentary Democracy, 1990 (Box-folder 156: 3)
- Europe
  - Benelux, 1992-2003 (Box-folder 156: 4)
  - UN Economic Commission for Europe, 1975-1996 (Box-folder 156: 5)
  - Public opinion, 1975-1993 (Box-folder 156: 6)
  - European integration, 1975-2003 (Box-folder 156: 7-9)
- North Atlantic Assembly, 1976-2001 (Box-folder 157: 1-3)
- NATO/NORAD, 1981-2003 (Box-folder 157: 4)
- Europe
  - European Space Administration, 1976-1992 (Box-folder 157: 5)
  - European Free Trade, 1980-1992 (Box-folder 157: 6)
  - Nordic Council, 1977 (Box-folder 157: 7)
- Black Sea Pact, 1992 (Box-folder 157: 8)
- Nuclear disarmament, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 157: 9-11)
- Workbook for Battelle Seminar and Study Program seminar on world politics and world business, 1981 (Box-folder 158: 1)
- "Seminar Notebook: World Business and World Politics,", 1982 (Box-folder 158: 2)
- The Federalist No. 4: Euro-Atlantic Review for a Federalist Democracy, 1984 November-December (Box-folder 158: 3)
- Issues and options, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 158: 4-5)
- The Atlantic Council Policy Papers
  - "Western Interests and U.S. Policy Options in the Middle East,", 1988 (Box-folder 158: 6)
  - "Defending Peace and Freedom: Toward Strategic Stability in the Year 2000,", 1987 (Box-folder 158: 7)
  - "U.S. Policy Towards Canada: Guidelines for the Next Decade,", 1987 (Box-folder 158: 8)
  - "U.S. International Leadership for the 21st Century: Building a National Foreign Affairs Constituency,", 1987 (Box-folder 158: 9)
  - "The Uruguay Round of Multilateral Trade Negotiations Under GATT: Policy Proposals on Trade and Services,", 1987 (Box-folder 158: 10)
  - "U.S. Policy Towards the Soviet Union: A Long-Term Western Perspective, 1987-2000," (Box-folder 158: 11)
  - "European Democratic Socialist Parties and NATO,", 1987 (Box-folder 158: 12)
  - "Combating International Terrorism: U.S.-Allied Cooperation and Political Will,", 1986 (Box-folder 158: 13)
- Investment in Excellence: An Application Guide by Louis Tice, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 159: 1-3)
- "Seminar Notebook: World Business and World Politics,", 1982 (Box-folder 159: 4)
- "BASICS Notebook: Generation and Use of Scenarios in Corporate Planning,", 1980 (Box-folder 159: 5-6)
- "Key Technologies: The 1980s,", 1981 (Box-folder 160: 1-2)
- "World Politics Monitor: Annual Review, 1981 (Box-folder 160: 3-4)
- University of Washington, 1986 (Box-folder 160: 5)
- Mid-Atlantic Clubs Network, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 161: 1-2)
- NATO peacemaking, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 161: 3)
- Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe (CSCE) and Organization for Security and Cooperation in Europe (OSCE), 1981-1996 (Box-folder 161: 4)
- "The New Tyrants,", 1990 (Box-folder 161: 5)
- NATO, Euro-Atlantic partnership, Russia relations, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 161: 6)
- Partnership for Peace (PFP), 1995 (Box-folder 161: 7)
- NATO Expansion, 1992-2003 (Box-folder 161: 8-9)
- Atlantic Community, Strategic Defense Initiative, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 161: 10)
- NATO, chemical weapons, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 161: 11)
- Coordinating Committee for Multilateral Export Controls (COCOM), 1996 (Box-folder 161: 12)
- Atlantic Community, arms control, Conventional, 1986-1996 (Box-folder 161: 13)
- NATO, espionage and intelligence, 1986 (Box-folder 161: 14)
- Globalization, 2003 (Box-folder 162: 1)
- North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1988-1998 (Box-folder 162: 2)
- Social Problems
  - Child care, 1992 (Box-folder 162: 3)
  - Civic culture, democracy, and political systems, 1975-1996 (Box-folder 162: 4)
  - Crisis in civilization, 1974-2004 (Box-folder 162: 5)
- Values, 1985-2003 (Box-folder 162: 6)
- Biographies of friends and associates, 1981-1995 (Box-folder 162: 7)
- Y.M.A.C. London, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 162: 8)
- Atlantic Pacific economy
  - Monetary, 1979-1998 (Box-folder 162: 9)
  - Monetary and investment, 1974-1999 (Box-folder 163: 1)
- Group of ten, 1986 (Box-folder 163: 3)
- Atlantic Pacific economy trade, 1974-2004 (Box-folder 163: 4-8)
- Social problems
  - Migration, 1980-1995 (Box-folder 164: 1)
  - Education, 1980-2002 (Box-folder 164: 2)
  - Art and taste, 1979 (Box-folder 164: 3)
  - Modernization, 1987-2002 (Box-folder 164: 4)
- Atlantic Pacific economy, 1966-1998 (Box-folder 164: 5-7)
- European monetary system, 1986-1996 (Box-folder 164: 8)
- Atlantic Pacific economy
  - Statistics, 1976-1995 (Box-folder 164: 9)
  - Policy coordination, 1975-1993 (Box-folder 164: 10)
  - Economic theory, 1980-1993 (Box-folder 164: 11)
  - Economic summits, 1990-2004 (Box-folder 164: 12-13)
  - Transnational investments, 1974-2002 (Box-folder 165: 1-2)
- Social problems
  - Minorities, 1979-1992 (Box-folder 165: 3)
  - Religion, 1980-2002 (Box-folder 165: 4)
  - Leadership, 1982-2001 (Box-folder 165: 5-7)
  - National Service, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 165: 8)
  - Space, 1982 (Box-folder 165: 9)
  - Public opinion, 1979-1999 (Box-folder 165: 10)
  - Culture, 1979-1996 (Box-folder 165: 11)
- Economy, reshaping industry, 1981 (Box-folder 166: 1)
- Economy, North-South relations (LDCs), 1974-2001 (Box-folder 166: 2-4)
- Atlantic Pacific economy, Washington State Economic Development, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 166: 5)
- Economy development, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 166: 6)
- Atlantic Pacific economy, Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD), 1972-2002 (Box-folder 166: 7-8)
- United States finance
  - Bechtels, 1986 (Box-folder 167: 1)
  - Bronfman, Edgar M., 1986 (Box-folder 167: 2)
  - Buffett, Warren E., 1986-1995 (Box-folder 167: 3)
  - Crown, Lester, 1986 (Box-folder 167: 4)
  - Davis, Marvin, 1986 (Box-folder 167: 5)
  - Newhouse, Samuel/Donald, 1986 (Box-folder 167: 6)
  - Gallo, 1986 (Box-folder 167: 7)
  - Getty, Gordon P., 1987 (Box-folder 167: 8)
  - Forbes 400 ranking, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 167: 9)
  - Overseas targets, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 167: 10)
  - Targets, possibilities, 1990 (Box-folder 167: 11)
  - Peter Marsden correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 167: 12)
  - Annenberg, Walter H., 1986 (Box-folder 167: 13)
  - Anschutz, P. F., 1986 (Box-folder 167: 14)
  - Anthony, Barbara Cox, 1986 (Box-folder 167: 15)
  - Bass family, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 167: 16)
  - Targets, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 167: 17-20)
  - Financial plans, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 167: 21)
  - Background information, 1987 (Box-folder 167: 22)
  - Steven Miller correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 168: 1)
  - Eastern Central Europe, 1993 (Box-folder 168: 2)
  - Operations, correspondence, 1987-2004 (Box-folder 168: 3)
  - Relevant groups, foundations, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 168: 4)
  - Rockefellers, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 168: 5)
  - Schoelkopf, Caroline Hunt, 1986 (Box-folder 168: 6)
  - Tisch, Laurance and Preston, 1986 (Box-folder 168: 7)
  - Walton, Samuel M., 1986-1990 (Box-folder 168: 8)
  - An Wang, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 168: 9)
  - Watson Jr., Thomas J., 1986 (Box-folder 168: 10)
  - Wexner, Leslie, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 168: 11)
  - Whitehead, John, 1987 (Box-folder 168: 12)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 168: 13)
  - Davidson correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 168: 14)
  - Hill, Margaret Hunt, 1986 (Box-folder 168: 15)
  - Hillman, Henry, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 168: 16)
  - Kluge, John W., 1986-1993 (Box-folder 168: 17)
  - Lefrak, Samuel J., 1988-1990 (Box-folder 168: 18)
  - Mars family, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 168: 19)
  - Mellon, Paul, 1986 (Box-folder 168: 20)
  - Packard, David, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 168: 21)
  - Perot, Henry Ross, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 168: 22)
  - Pritzker, Robert and Jay, 1986 (Box-folder 168: 23)
  - Helmsley, Harry, 1986 (Box-folder 168: 24)
  - Hewlett, William, 1986 (Box-folder 168: 25)
- John M. Davis, Vol. III, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 169: 1-2)
- John M. Davis, Vol. II, 1970-1994 (Box-folder 169: 3-7)
- U.S. 21st Century
  - Board meeting, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 169: 8)
  - Germany, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 169: 9)
  - Japan, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 169: 10)
- Directives Richtelinien, 1985 (Box-folder 170: 1)
- Accord Abkommen, 1984 (Box-folder 170: 2)
- Die Deutsch-Französische Zusammenarbeit/La coopération Franco-Allemande, 1983 (Box-folder 170: 3)
- "Teaching About Collective Security and Conflict,", 1971 (Box-folder 170: 4)
- "Improving the Teaching of World Affairs,", 1963 (Box-folder 170: 5)
- "International Education: A Documentary History,", 1960 (Box-folder 170: 6)
- "U.S. College-Sponsored Programs Abroad,", 1973 (Box-folder 170: 7)
- "A Guide to Understanding World Affairs,", 1966 (Box-folder 170: 8)
- "World Politics in the 1980s,", 1983 (Box-folder 170: 9-10)
- Encounter Magazine, 1986-1988 (Box 171)
- Encounter Magazine, 1983-1985 (Box 172)
- "Undergraduate Study Abroad: Report of the Consultative Service on U.S. Undergraduate Study Abroad,", 1964 (Box 172)
- "National Negotiating Styles,", 1987 (Box 172)
- Hearings Before the Task Force on International Education of the Committee on Education and Labor, 1966 (Box 172)
- "The University Looks Abroad: Approaches to World Affairs at Six American Universities,", 1965 (Box 172)
- "International Education: Past, Present, Problems and Prospects, 1966 (Box 172)
- "Olmsted Plan for Bainbridge Island,", 1991-1992 (Box-folder 173: 1)
- Power outages, Washington State, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 173: 2)
- John M. Davis, Vol. I, 1975-1994 (Box-folder 173: 3-5)
- John M. Davis, 21st Century Trust, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 173: 6-7)
- John M. Davis, Seattle Committees for a Community of Democracies (CCD), 1982-1991 (Box-folder 173: 8)
- "Jahrbuch für Jugendreisen und Internationalen Jugendaustausch,", 1981 (Box 174)
- "Diploma: International Schools and University Entrance,", 1968 (Box 174)
- "The Historian's Contribution to Anglo-American Misunderstanding,", 1966 (Box 174)
- "Intercultural Communication: A Reader,", 1972 (Box 174)
- "Education in Europe: Civics and European Education at the Primary and Secondary Level,", 1963 (Box 174)
- "International Educational and Cultural Exchange,", 1969-1972 (Box 174)
- "Intercommunication Among Nations and Peoples,", 1973 (Box 174)
- "Association des Instituts d'Etudes Européennes Annuaire,", 1968 (Box 174)
- "The Professional School and World Affairs: Report of the Task Force on Business Administration and Public Administration,", 1967 (Box 174)
- "A Unique Contribution to International Relations: The Story of Wilton Park,", 1973 (Box 174)
- "Integrity in the College Curriculum: A Report to the Academic Community,", 1985 (Box 174)
- "Undergraduate Education in Foreign Affairs,", 1962 (Box 174)
- "The American Assembly: Cultural Affairs and Foreign Relations,", 1963 (Box 174)
- "The Geopolitics of Information: How Western Culture Dominates the World,", 1980 (Box 174)
- "Global Dimensions in U.S. Education: The Community,", 1972 (Box 174)
- "The University and World Affairs,", 1960 (Box 174)
- "The College and World Affairs,", 1964 (Box 174)